[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Apocalypse Log 12]
Hang in there.
I'll find a safe place to treat your wound.
I'm fine.
Put me down.
I can walk on my own.
You're still acting tough.
If you fall again, I'll have to carry you anyway.
The arrow was poisoned.
The toxic blood is finally cleared out.
You...
You jerk.
Meeting you was my misfortune.
Get well soon.
Your fever is finally gone.
Leave me be.
Go.
It's yours now.
Protect yourself.
I'm going with you,
but that doesn't mean I'm your prisoner.
Reaching the headquarters as soon as possible...
is best for everyone.
Don't forget.
He's a hunter.
You're just his prey.
Just a lab rat he needs to catch.
Detect if the target is an immune.
Target confirmed as an immune.
Taming a dog that bites is simple.
You just have to pull out its fangs.
You bastard.
And here I was, trusting you and thinking we were friends.
I only need to ensure you're alive.
Let go, you bastard!
Don't force me to use the methods I use on others...
Let's go.
If you stay any longer, you won't be able to leave.
Now is your best chance.
Lin Zai...
Don't leave me behind.
No, please, no...
Mom, Dad...
You're useless.
If you can't get up on your own,
then just rot right here.
Wait for death.
Don't go.
Don't leave me behind.
Why did you come back?
You could have just left.
Even if you had abandoned me today,
I wouldn't have been surprised.
I'm used to it.
Used to what?
Used to being abandoned.
Discarding others to save yourself...
Isn't that just human instinct?
In critical moments, even your own parents,
and comrades you've faced death with...
cannot be trusted.
You...
Why did you come back?
Lie.
I'm not like them.
I have a heart.
- S-So... - Listen, Lie.
If I go with you, will I die?
I will protect you...
with my life.
Is that enough?